Preliminary Guide to the Craufurd D. W. Goodwin papers, 1960-2010 UA.29.02.0010
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Container List
  - HES call for papers (Box 25)
  - Contributed papers (Box 25)
  - Bibliography (Box 25)
  - Misc. notes and versions of various chapters (Box 25)
  - Lyon, Robert (Box 25)
  - Economics Department, 1969-1970 (Box 25)
  - Brookings Institute Conference, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Papers submitted by:
    - Hines, Samuel (Box 25)
    - Skillen, James (Box 25)
    - Collier, Charlie (Box 25)
    - Goody, W. K. (Box 25)
    - Heeren, John W. (Box 25)
    - Breytopraak, G. (Box 25)
    - Petridis, Ray (Box 25)
    - Forness, Larry (Box 25)
    - No author identified (Box 25)
  - A Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - ACLS (Box 26)
  - B Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - Bevin/Mcarthur (Box 26)
  - Brookings Institute Agricultural Study (Box 26)
  - C Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - Canadian Economic Talks (Box 26)
  - Canadian Studies (Box 26)
  - Chancellor's Advisory Committee on Institutional Advancement, University Relations, and Alumni Relations (Box 26)
  - D Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - Duke University Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - E Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - Economics Department Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - Economics Papers (Box 26)
  - F Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - Fondness and Frustration (Box 26)
  - Friends of the Library (Box 26)
  - G Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - The Graduate School (Box 26)
  - H Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - 1988 Hansman Paper on Economics (Box 26)
  - Harvard University Board of Overseers, Dec. 7, 1986 (Box 26)
  - HES
    - Meetings, 1985 (Box 26)
    - Paper, 1985 (Box 26)
    - 1986 (Box 26)
    - Distinguished Fellow Award (Box 26)
    - Meetings, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Conference, Charlottesville, Va., May 23-26, 1983 (Box 26)
    - Duke University Meeting, 1982 (Box 26)
  - IIE (Box 26)
  - J Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - K Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - L Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - Mc Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - M Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - Macarthur Foundation (Box 26)
  - N Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - NATSA (Box 26)
  - O Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - P Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - R Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - House Republican Research Committee, 1984 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 26)
  - S miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Sanford, Terry (Box 27)
  - Schumpeter Society (Box 27)
  - South Atlantic Quarterly (Box 27)
  - Southern Economics Association (Box 27)
  - T miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Talks, 1984-1985 (Box 27)
  - Truman Centennial Symposium, Washington D.C., September 7-8, 1984 (Box 27)
  - Undergraduate research assistantship program (Box 27)
  - V miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Vanderbilt project (TVA) (Box 27)
  - W miscellaneous (Box 27)
  - Rhetoric of Economics, Wellesley College, April 17-19, 1986
    - The Heterogeneity of Economic Discourse (Box 27)
  - Woodrow Wilson Center Conference June 6, 1977 (Box 27)
  - Woodrow Wilson International Security Studies (Box 27)
  - Academic handbook (Box 28)
  - Abroad and Beyond (Box 28)
  - ACLS (Box 28)
  - Barber Conference (Box 28)
  - Decline and Renewal (Box 28)
  - Brookings Energy (Box 28)
  - Copy center (Box 28)
  - Economics and Empire (Box 28)
  - Energy project (Box 28)
  - Fulbright review (Box 28)
  - GMF (Box 28)
  - HES (Box 29)
  - JACIP (Box 29)
  - Leningrad conference (Box 29)
  - Lodwijks, John (Box 29)
  - Marginal Revolution in Economic Thought, conference (Box 29)
  - Mellon (Box 29)
  - Menger conference (Box 29)
  - Middlebury conference (Box 29)
  - Middlebury people (Box 29)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 29)
  - Missing the Boat (Box 29)
  - Preventing Professional and Intellectual Decay (Box 29)
  - Search Out the Secret Parts (Box 29)
  - Study Abroad (Box 29)
  - Missing the Boat: Page proofs index (Box 30)
    - Earlier version (Box 30)
  - General Cambridge University Press correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 30)
  - Cambridge University Press, History of Economic Thought Series
    - January 1979 - February 1982 (Box 30)
    - March 1982 - December 1982 (Box 30)
    - January 1983 - December 1985 (Box 30)
  - Jolink, Albert (Cambridge Univ. Press) (Box 30)
  - Mirowski, Philip (Cambridge Univ. Press, More Hear than Light) (Box 30)
  - Pew ENS Volumes Westview (Box 31)
  - Grant Proposal June 1990 (Box 31)
  - Pew Grants in Public Policy 1990 (List of Institutions) (Box 31)
  - Investments Pew ENS Grants (Box 31)
  - Correspondence Pew Charitable Trusts (Box 31)
  - ENS Colloquium Philadelphia (First Annual) (Box 31)
  - Inquiry to Pew Re: Support for Minority Recruitment (Box 31)
  - Diplomatic Training Initiative (Box 31)
  - Phase I, II, and III ENS Correspondence (Box 31)
  - Proposals 10 Universities, March 1988 (Box 31)
  - ENS and GS Bridge Project (Transitional Program) (Box 31)
  - Meeting (ENS Transitional), IIE, D. C. (Box 31)
  - Proposal Adams, et al. ENS Transitional Program (Box 31)
  - Proposal Leitzel, et al. ENS Transitional Program (Box 31)
  - Proposal Marshall ENS Transitional Program (Box 31)
  - Proposal Bienen, et al. ENS Transitional Program (Box 31)
  - Proposal Hellman and Pyle ENS Transitional Program (Box 31)
  - Proposal Baldwin, Jervis, and Snyder ENS Transitional Program (Box 31)
  - Proposal Intriligator and Quester ENS Transitional Program (Box 31)
  - Budget Pew ENS Grants (Box 31)
  - Budget March Conference, The Breakers (Box 31)
  - Budget IIE Meeting, Washington D. C., ENS Transitional Program (Box 31)
  - Budget Defense Procurement (Box 31)
  - Budget Historical Roots (Box 31)
  - Budget Snidal's Working Group, University of Chicago (Box 31)
  - Budget Political Economy (Box 31)
  - Budget Adam's Working Group, University of Pennsylvania (Box 31)
  - Budget Bienen's Working Group, Princeton University (Box 31)
  - Budget Tirole's Working Group, M. I. T. (Box 31)
  - Goodwin, Craufurd Misc. Correspondence (Box 31)
  - Jim Leitzel Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 31)
  - Leitzel, Jim Miscellaneous Info. (Box 34)
  - Evaluation ENS Project (Box 34)
  - Mattis, Evelyn (Miscellaneous) (Box 34)
  - ASSA Meeting December 30, 1990 (Jim Leitzel) (Box 34)
  - Power and Security Henry Bienen (Box 32)
  - Pew ENS General File (Box 34)
  - Pew ENS Bibliography (Box 34)
  - Budget Marshall, et. al. (Transitional Program), 1992 (Box 34)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted until 2062.
  - Budget Downs, et. al. (Snidal) (Transitional Program), 1992 (Box 34)
  - Budget Snyder, et.al. (Transition Program) (Box 34)
  - Publications Pew ENS Program (Box 34)
  - Working Groups ENS (Box 34)
  - ENS Historical Roots Project Craufurd Goodwin (Box 34)
  - Pew History, 1990 (Box 34)
  - Working Group: Defense and the Macroeconomy (Adams) (Box 34)
  - Working Group: Power and Security (Bienen) (Box 34)
  - Working Group: Conflict and Cooperation (Snidel) (Box 34)
  - Working Group: Defense and the Microeconomy (Tirole), 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Project Directors ENS (Box 34)
  - Boston, Sept. 22-23, 1989 (Box 34)
  - Correspondence Related to "The Breakers" Conference (Box 34)
  - Doing Good and Spreading the Gospel (Economic) -Correspondence (Box 33)
  - HES
    - Meeting, 1987 (Box 33)
    - Meeting, Toronto 1988 (Box 33)
    - Toronto Papers, 1988 (Box 33)
    - AEA Roundtable, August 1989 (Box 33)
    - Meeting, Richmond 1989 (Box 33)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 33)
  - Correspondence - IIE Overseas Higher Education Volume (Box 33)
  - SEA Conference, 1970
    - 1990 (Box 33)
    - 1991 (Box 33)
  - SEA Papers, 1991 (Box 33)
  - Academic Council (Box 33)
  - University Planning Committee (Box 33)
  - A-Z Miscellaneous, 1985-1990 (Box 32)
  - Academic Council, 1987-1990 (Box 35)
  - Academic Standards Committee, 1990-1993 (Box 35)
  - ACLS 1986 Meeting, April 9-10,1986 (Box 35)
  - ACLS 1987 Meeting, April 16, 1987 (Box 35)
  - ACLS 1990 Meeting (Box 35)
  - Agency for International Development, 1990 (Box 35)
  - Austrian Economics Seminar (1989), March 22, 1988 (Box 35)
  - Bevan, William, 1989-1992 (Box 35)
  - Brandeis University Visit, October 1989 (Box 35)
  - Carter Mondale Policy Planning Group, 1976 (Box 35)
  - Cole, Taylor, Obituary Piece, 1991 (Box 35)
  - Commencement, May 4, 1986 (Box 35)
  - Computer Science Search Committee, 1992 (Box 35)
  - Convocation, 1992 (Box 35)
  - Copier, 1988-1990 (Box 35)
  - Council of Graduate Schools, 1988 (Meeting Nov. 29 - Dec. 2, 1988) (Box 35)
  - Council for International Exchange of Scholars, 1988 1992 (Box 35)
  - Economics Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 35)
  - German Marshall Fund Report, May 30, 1990 (Box 35)
  - German Marshall Fund Report, July 1990 (Box 35)
  - Graduate Schools (Association of), 1989 (Box 35)
  - HES Nominations, 1992 (Box 35)
  - HES Meeting, George Mason University, 1992 (Box 35)
  - HES Meeting Univ. of MD, College Park, 1991 (Box 35)
  - HES Meeting Lexington, VA June 22-25, 1990 (Box 35)
  - IIE Trends, 1992-1993 (Box 35)
  - IIE Billing (backup), 1992 (Box 35)
  - International Political Economy, 1992 (Box 35)
  - Friends of the Library, 1986-1992 (Box 35)
  - Pew Charitable Trusts, June - September, 1988 (Box 36)
  - Pew - ENS, 1990 (Box 36)
  - Philanthropy Center, 1986-1989 (Box 36)
  - Placement Office, University Review of, 1989-1992 (Box 36)
  - Plympton, Ann, 1986-1987 (Box 36)
  - Reid, Gavin C., 1990-1991 (Box 36)
  - Sloan Foundation, Alfred P., 1990 (Box 36)
  - University of Tennessee, Evaluation of Economics Department, 1986-1989 (Box 36)
  - Truman Library, 1986-1988 (Box 36)
  - U.S. Institute for Peace, 1992 (Box 36)
  - War and Gender Conference, 1992 (Box 36)
  - Williams, Henry George Lecture, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Woodrow Wilson Center International Scholars Selection Panel, 1988-1992 (Box 36)
- Accession (2009-0191), 11 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Accession (2009-0191) (12375 items; 16.5 lin. ft.; dated 1960s-2000) consists largely of Ford Foundation materials on a variety of subjects, as well as additional Duke administrative and Economics Department files, and research files collected by Goodwin on Australian and international economics. The Ford Foundation files include correspondence, reports, grant and policy papers, and other materials relating to human rights, international relations, education, and public policy, among other subjects.
  This addition was accessioned according to Rubenstein Library procedures and then added to the existing University Archives collection. It is unprocessed; the container list below reflects the original condition of the materials at the time of their arrival at the Library.
  - Truman administration energy policy research notes (Box 37)
  - Ford Foundation consultant work (Box 37)
    Includes, but is not limited to, materials (information papers, discussion papers, reports, etc.) on human rights; international migration and refugees; United States foreign policy; the world economy; and arts and culture.
  - Philanthropic choices, style, and methods: a 25 year review, 1976 (Box 37)
  - Staff responses to Alexander Heard's Sept. 24 memorandum, 'Next Steps in Planning for the Foundation's Future,' vol. 1-2, 1976 (Box 37)
  - Ford Foundation interoffice memos, 1970s (Box 37)
  - Ford Foundation materials
    - Latin American program (Box 37)
    - Education for Development (Box 37)
    - Study Abroad (Box 37)
    - International Affairs (Box 37)
    - United Nations Association (Box 38)
    - Craufurd Goodwin notes (Box 38)
    - Public policy debate about Mexico, 1990s (Box 38)
    - Pew Charitable Trusts, 1994 (Box 38)
    - Reports and policy papers
      - Education (Box 38)
      - International economics (Box 38)
      - Overseas Development Council (Box 38)
      - Asia and Latin America (Box 38)
    - Correspondence and memos with other departments, 1980s (Box 38)
    - Photocopied correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 38)
    - New York Times Magazine article, 1978 (Box 39)
    - Third world education, 1983 (Box 39)
    - Common Problems competition grant, MIT, 1977 (Box 39)
    - Economics Policy meeting, 1979 (Box 39)
    - European Policy study (Box 39)
    - Public policy and notes (Box 39)
    - Pew/Duke democracy project (Box 39)
    - Handwritten notes: CSAI, IEO, 1970s (4 steno pads) (Box 39)
  - Duke University administrative work
    - International Executive Committee (Box 39)
    - International Affairs Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
    - Internationalization (Box 39)
    - History of Economic Thought group, 1997 (Box 39)
    - Correspondence with Peggy Blumenthal, Institute of International Education, 1989-1990s (Box 39)
    - Commonwealth Program, 1990s (Box 39)
    - CIES, Great Persons, 1992 (Box 39)
    - Chicago Symposium, 1992 (Box 39)
    - Professor Brems file, 1990s (Box 39)
    - Asian International University, 1997 (Box 39)
    - Trustee nominations, 1996-1997 (Box 39)
    - Kreps Chair, 1997 (Box 39)
    - Economics undergraduate curriculum, 1994-1995 (Box 39)
    - Royaumont conference, 1974 (Box 39)
    - Social Science Research Council, Human Capital, 1997 (Box 40)
    - Social Science Research Council workshop, 1993 (Box 40)
    - Hymer paper comments (Box 40)
    - Center for Commonwealth Studies, 1972-1977 (Box 40)
    - Fisher, Irving (collected works) (Box 40)
    - Economics Department correspondence (SENSITIVE), 1990-1997 (Box 40)
    - Economics Department self-study, 1975-1976 (Box 40)
    - NC Center for International Studies, 1969-1970s (Box 40)
    - Duke University Press Board, 1970s-1980s (Box 40)
  - Research and notes for writings
    - African materials (Box 40)
    - African ideas (Box 40)
    - Royal African Company (Box 40)
    - Uncarded notes re: colonies (Box 40)
    - Carded journals; notes for Image of Australia (Box 40)
    - Carded books and pamphlets about Australia (Box 41)
    - Materials about Australia (Box 41)
  - National Science Foundation grant (Box 41)
  - Pew Charitable Trust (Box 41)
  - Overseas Higher Education and Development (Box 41)
  - IIE (Box 41)
  - Personal correspondence, 1972 (2 folders) (Box 41)
  - Ford Foundation materials
    - Ford Foundation and International Affairs program (Box 41)
    - Oral histories (transcribed) (Box 41)
    - Congress for Cultural Freedom (Box 41)
    - Citizen education, 1960s (Box 41)
    - General materials, 1980s (Box 41)
  - National Archives and Records Administration research (Box 41)
  - Sanford for President, 1976 (Box 41)
  - Ford Foundation and International Affairs draft, 1986 (Box 41)
  - Program of Training and Research in International Affairs proposal, 1963-1964 (2 folders) (Box 41)
  - Ford Foundation materials and reports (Box 41)
  - Ford Foundation, miscellaneous (Box 41)
  - Duke Economics and administration, miscellaneous (Box 41)
  - Correspondence, personal, 1971 (Box 41)
  - Correspondence, personnel, 1971-1976 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence, personal, 1970s (Box 42)
  - Stratton trip to USSR, 1971 (Box 42)
  - Ford Foundation materials, including but not limited to:
    - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholarship (Box 42)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 42)
    - Brookings Institution (Box 42)
    - Craufurd Goodwin miscellaneous files (Box 42)
    - Queries, 1972-1974 (Box 42)
    - EIA; Europe (Box 42)
    - Canada (Box 42)
    - Energy (Box 42)
    - Travel, 1990s (Box 42)
    - Notes on the internal audit (Box 42)
    - International security (Box 42)
    - Arms control (Box 42)
  - On retirement from the EIA, 1977 (Box 42)
  - Comments and correspondence, 1970s (Box 42)
  - Truman energy policy research (Box 42)
  - Ford Foundation consulting files, 1989-1990 (Box 43)
  - Chron files (correspondence), 1970-1974 (Box 43)
  - Ford Foundation materials (Box 44)
    - International economy (Box 44)
    - Proposal reviews (Box 44)
    - International Affairs, 1985 (Box 44)
  - Duke materials
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 44)
    - Sabbatical leave, 1967-1968 (Box 44)
    - Economics Department, 1970-1985 (Box 44)
    - Duke and Rockefeller job, 1960s (Box 44)
    - Canada Council, 1960s (Box 44)
    - York University, 1960s (Box 44)
    - Australia trip, 1960s (Box 44)
    - Craufurd Goodwin speech notes (Box 44)
    - Course materials (Box 44)
      Files including Labor Assumption, History of Economic Thought, Economics booklist, History of Social Science seminar, International Studies, Economics and Government, Chancellor's Advisory Committee.
    - Journal of Economic Literature (Box 44)
    - International Economics Images (2 folders) (Box 44)
    - Publications and professional meetings, 1971 (Box 44)
    - Schumpeter article, 1984 (Box 44)
    - Nixon Library, 1981 (Box 44)
    - Southeastern Economic Association, 1971 (Box 44)
    - Research files/papers (3 folders) (Box 44)
    - Origin of History of Political Economy, 1960s (Box 44)
  - Harry Truman Library research on IOC (3 folders) (Box 45)
  - African Economic Research Consortium, 1990s (Box 45)
  - Oxford Companion to American Military History, 1995 (Box 45)
  - Ford Foundation: general expense reports, evaluations, 1990 (Box 45)
  - Subject files
    - Economists and railways in Australia (3 folders) (Box 45)
    - Evolutionary theory article (Box 45)
    - Universities-Australia notes (Box 45)
    - Economic development (Box 45)
    - Socialism and labor problems (Box 45)
    - Development of science (Box 45)
    - Comm. policy (Box 45)
    - Land policy (Box 45)
    - Population (Box 45)
    - Banking (Box 45)
    - Sec. materials (Box 46)
    - Statistics (Box 46)
    - Transport (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - De Lissa (Box 46)
    - Australia, miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Chapter additions (Box 46)
    - Work to be carded and typed (Box 46)
    - Trade cycles (Box 46)
    - Burwood Coat Coy Ltd. (Box 46)
    - Edward Gibbon Wakefield (Box 46)
    - Population Studies in Australia (Box 46)
  - Duke History of Economic Thought (Box 46)
  - Economics Department plan, 1994 (Box 46)
  - Ford Foundation materials
    - Overseas Development Council, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Asia/India, 1992 (Box 46)
    - International Affairs, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Latin America, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Human rights and governance, 1991 (Box 46)
  - Caldwell Program (Box 46)
  - Ford Foundation, Teaching Undergraduate Social Science, 2000 (Box 46)
  - Japan Foundation Center (Box 46)
  - Miscellaneous loose materials (Box 46)
  - Miscellaneous Duke materials, 1970s (Box 46)
  - History of Economics group, 1970s (Box 46)
  - International Education: testimony before the House subcommittee, 1991 (Box 47)
  - Internationalization paper (with Meardon) (Box 47)
  - Cyberpunk, 1990s (Box 47)
  - Baumgardner, James, 1994-1995 (Box 47)
  - Committee on Teaching in Tenure and Promotion process (Box 47)
  - Southern Economics Association, 1990s (Box 47)
  - Schumpeter Conference/Japan trip, 1992 (Box 47)
  - Senior Year Committee, 1990s (Box 47)
  - Center for International Studies (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Duke Library's Economists' Papers Project
    - Library (2 folders) (Box 47)
    - Menger papers (Box 47)
    - Morganstern papers, 1988 (Box 47)
    - Library project (3 folders) (Box 47)
    - National Humanities Center, 1990s (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - International Student and Institutional Policy, Loyola, 1983 (Box 47)
  - Foreign Students in the U.S., 1982 (Box 47)
  - Ford Foundation, 1984 (Box 47)
  - Commencement, 1985 (Box 47)
  - Graduate School miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Sabbatical Leave, 1967-1968 (6 folders) (Box 47)
  - History of Political Economy (Box 47)
  - Bill Allen (Box 47)
- Accession (2009-0240), 5 boxes
  Accession (2009-0240) (2250 items; 3.0 lin. ft.; dated 1960s-2000) includes a variety of materials relating to the Ford Foundation and Duke's Economics Department, as well as personal correspondence, History of Political Economy journal materials, research with fellow economist Michael Nacht, and correspondence about the Cambridge University Press.
  - Personal (Box 48)
  - Personal correspondence (Box 48)
  - Correspondence about articles and manuscripts, 1990s (Box 48)
  - Name files
    - Ascher, William, 1993 (Box 48)
    - Bronfennbrenner, Martin (Box 48)
    - Calhoun, Craig (Box 48)
    - Coats, A.W. (Box 48)
    - Cook, Philip (Box 48)
    - Cook, Simon (Box 48)
    - Hamowy, Ronald (Box 48)
    - Glasner, David (Box 48)
    - Knight, Frank, 1972 (Box 48)
    - Levy, David (Box 48)
    - Patinkin, Don (Box 48)
    - Perlman, Mark, Nobel Awards in Economics, 1994-1998 (Box 48)
    - Samuelson, Paul (Box 48)
    - Shionoya, Yuichi (Box 48)
    - Sutton, Francis, 1989 (Box 48)
  - Ford Foundation materials (Box 49)
    - Poland and USSR trip, 1971 (Box 49)
    - Brazil report, August 1990 (Box 49)
    - Latin American Higher Education report, 1990 (Box 49)
    - Argentina report (with Michael Nacht), 1991 (Box 49)
    - Education and Culture, 1991 (Box 49)
    - Latin America, 1991 (Box 49)
    - International Affairs, 1991 (Box 49)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 49)
    - Silk (Box 49)
    - Duke grant (Box 49)
    - American Society of International Law (Box 49)
  - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 50)
  - Sasakawa Forum (Box 50)
  - Pew Charitable Trust: economic education in Central and Eastern Europe (Box 50)
  - Pew global society program (Box 50)
  - Institute for International Economics, 1984 (Box 50)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1999-2000 (Box 50)
  - Duke materials
    - Faculty, 1982 (Box 50)
    - Lewin matter, 1983 (Box 50)
    - Duke University Libraries Musgrove Collection, 1961 (Box 50)
    - Canadian studies (Box 50)
    - International studies (Box 50)
  - Luce professor, 1994 (3 folders) (Box 51)
  - Institute for International Economics media, 1992-1993 (Box 51)
  - Guide to the History of Economic Thought (HET) (Box 51)
  - Economics of Survival, 1968 (Box 52)
  - The Forgotten Payoff, report by Craufurd Goodwin and Michael Nacht (Box 52)
  - Abe Followship program, 2000 (Box 52)
  - Harvard Public Finance group (Box 52)
  - U. Penn MLA, 1997 (Box 52)
  - Cambridge University Press (CUP) name files
    - Andvig, Jens (Box 52)
    - Birner, Jack (Box 52)
    - Day, Colin (Box 52)
    - Dooley, Peter C. (Box 52)
    - Egger, John B. (Box 52)
    - Ekelund, B. Robert and Hebert, F. Robert (Box 52)
    - Emmett, Ross B. (Box 52)
    - Evensky, Jerry (Box 52)
    - Hammond, J. Daniel, 1992 (Box 52)
    - Hammond Proposal, June 1999 (Box 52)
    - Harrison, Paul (Box 52)
    - Irwin, Douglas A. (Box 52)
    - Valdes, Juan Gabriel (Box 52)
    - Vaughn, Karen (Box 52)
- Accession UA2017-0030, 1990-2010, undated; 4
  - Syllabi (Box 53)
  - Binder about Bloomsbury exhibit at Nasher, (includes CD or DVD), 2008-2009 (Box 53)
  - Speech given at Yale Center for British Art, "Bloomsbury Economics" (Box 53)
  - Cambridge University press royalty statements (Box 53)
  - HES (Box 53)
  - Hope 40, 2010 (Box 53)
  - Graduate Liberal Studies Advisory Committee Retreat (Box 53)
  - Institute for International Economics Board of Directors Meeting, Feb 2, 1990, 1990 February 02 (Box 53)
  - Henry Luce Professorship Program evaluation, 1994 (Box 53)
  - International Investment in Human Capital, Goodwin, editor (Box 53)
  - History of Social Sciences at Duke University brochure (Box 53)
  - Goodwin's dissertation, "Canadian Economic Thought." (Box 53)
  - 2 reels of microfilm (contents unknown) (Box 53)
  - History of Economics best article plaque (Box 53)
  - Reprints (articles by Goodwin) (Box 54)
  - Correspondence (unfoldered (Box 54)
  - "Walter Lippman, Public Economist" manuscript by Goodwin (Box 54)
  - Index cards (bibliography) (Box 54)
  - Teaching and other awards (Box 54)
  - Items collected from desk (set aside by Bruce Caldwell) (Box 54)
  - Writings, reprints, and drafts (Box 55)
  - Writings, reprints, and notes (Box 56)
  - Subject files (Box 56)
  - Correspondence (some unfoldered) (Box 57)
  - Luce Foundation grant files (Box 57)
  - Subject files (Box 57)
  - Correspondence (some unfoldered) (Box 58)